{
    "subject": "resource/Ljanik",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Village",
    "human_readable": "Ljanik is a Village.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9824765920639038,
            "question": "Is Ljanik a city or a village?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7992822527885437,
            "question": "What type of location is Ljanik?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27979540824890137,
            "question": "How is a village different from a town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.255137175321579,
            "question": "Can you name some activities commonly associated with villages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23892638087272644,
            "question": "Provide an example of another village."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2151506394147873,
            "question": "Can you describe the lifestyle in a village?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21111540496349335,
            "question": "What characteristics define a village?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15325869619846344,
            "question": "Are there any famous villages in the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11577047407627106,
            "question": "What is the population size of a typical village?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11287593096494675,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by villages today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ljanik is a Village.",
            "html": "dbpedia_534_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population size of a typical village?",
            "html": "dbpedia_534_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous villages in the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_534_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What characteristics define a village?",
            "html": "dbpedia_534_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_534_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text explicitly states that Ljanik \"is a village\" multiple times.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Ljanik is indeed a village, located in the municipality of Pre\u0161evo, Serbia. Therefore, the statement \"Ljanik is a Village\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}